[{"question": " good, you guys are all here!", "answer": " hey! what's up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " well, i have a job interview at ralph lauren tomorrow!", "answer": " congratulations! ohh, that's great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " i know!", "answer": " boy, that guy's underwear sucks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " wh-what?!", "answer": " i got this pair marked excess, i gotta tell ya, there was no room for excess anything in there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " anyway, i'm going to be the coordinator of the woman's collection, i'll work right under the director, it's the perfect, perfect job for me!", "answer": " wow! well, if you nail the interview, you'll get it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " you wanna work on your interview skills?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " o-okay!", "answer": " okay! all right, let's start with the handshake. hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " very good handshake, good wrist action.", "answer": " let me try.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " did i squeeze it too hard?", "answer": " let's just say, i'm glad i'm not chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " that's right ross, i can see you in your new apartment! and you can see me! same as yesterday,  same as the day before.", "answer": " is he doing his shark attack bit yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  very funny ross! very life-like and funny. okay.  oh no-no-no, i wasn't waving at you lady.   whoa, maybe i was! hey, monica, this totally hot girl in ross's building is flirting with me.", "answer": " get in there man! flirt back, mix it up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " yeah, i-i-i'm down with that.  okay, here goes.  how  you  a-doin'?   it worked! she's waving me over.  okay, i-i-i'll be right over. let's see, she's on the third floor\u009a", "answer": "  wow! she is pretty, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " hey joey! great stuff huh?", "answer": " this is your place?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " ugh!!", "answer": " what happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " we've lost visual contact with the suspect.", "answer": " okay, now i've really have to go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " but it's just so unfair that our date has to get cut short just 'cause some guy shot at a store clerk.", "answer": " i know, but it's my job, sweethart!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " okay, then maybe i can come too!", "answer": " suspect has just emerged naked from the sewer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " bye-bye.", "answer": " 'kay, bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh god!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " oh i just miss him so much!", "answer": " wow! for just a week you guys are really close, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " yeah, it's weird. i can't help it though he's so sweet, he's like this little puppy dog, y'know? but like a really tough one that shots bad guys. ohh, i just love beginning parts of relationships, y'know?! you just like can't keep your hands off each other.", "answer": " i know it is the best.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " so-so how long did that last for you and chandler?", "answer": " what? it's still going on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " come on, seriously! when did it end?", "answer": " i-i am serious, i mean, we're, we're all over each other all the time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " okay, you know where you are better than i do. i was just curious.", "answer": "   what don't you just calm down phoebe! all right?! why don\u0092t you just get all your facts before you run around telling everybody that you're the only hot couple!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": "  god, i woke the beast. sorry.  i was wrong obviously, i just\u0097i misspoke. it's okay.", "answer": " oh no, it is okay, i mean as long as you know that chandler and i are also very hot and fiery, just as hot as you! i mean our flame, whew, is on fire!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  hey monica, here's your broom back.", "answer": " you are so cute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh hey, how'd the interview go?", "answer": " ugh, horrible! i did the stupidest, most embarrassing thing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " did you tell the guy you wanted to have sex with his wife and then fall right out of your chair?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " so what happened?", "answer": " ugh, it was horrible! and-and the interview part went so well, y'know? i even made him laugh. he said something about a boat and i was like, \"well, yeah! if you've got enough life jackets!\"  trust me, it was actually, it was very funny. anyway, so we were saying good-bye and ugh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " what happened?", "answer": "  all right, we were shaking hands and he kinda leaned toward me\u009a y'know maybe he was going to open the door, but i totally miss read him and i uhhh\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " you kissed him?!", "answer": " well, i didn't know what else to do!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " well you coulda tried, not kissing him.", "answer": " thanks chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": "  hey rach, a guy from ralph lauren called, you got a second interview!", "answer": " i can't believe it! i got a second interview!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " i bet that kiss isn't looking like such a big mistake now, is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " what-what, wait a minute, you don't think that's why he wants me back?", "answer": " yeah!  no?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " a kiss? what are you talking about?", "answer": " i accidentally kissed him in the interview, and now he wants me back y'know of course, 'cause \"let's bring the girl back who kisses everybody!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " come on, rach.", "answer": " oh my god! what if he thinks i'm the kind of girl that-that would just sleep with him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " he probably wants you back because you're right for the job.", "answer": " maybe. i-i don't know\u0097oh god, how could i be so stupid?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh rachel look, don't say that, i think you just need a hug from joey. come on. come on.  she's back! hot girl's back!", "answer": " ohh, well i'm not totally back yet, but thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " damnit!! did you move?!", "answer": " yes. i lived with you guys for a while and then i found this place.  i'm ross.  the old man: yes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  uhh do you happen to have a hot girl in there? the old man: no. i'm all alone.", "answer": " yeah. sorry about that.  oh, hey little girl. uhh, is-is your mommy, or sister, or babysitter by any chance a hot girl? the little girl: daddy!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " hi rachel!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " it's really nice to see you again.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " just ah\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " excuse me?", "answer": " here let me\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " okay-okay that-that's amazing. how did you know that?", "answer": " you got ink on your lip.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": "  so what do you say, maybe sometime i hold your gun?", "answer": " i don't know man, we're really not supposed to do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " yeah, i'm gonna say no.", "answer": " phoebe, do you want to go see a movie after dinner tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " oh we can't, we already have plans.", "answer": " what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " well, same thing we did all day, hang out at gary's apartment. he is so amazing, we never left the bedroom. but have fun at the movie.", "answer": "  oh, we're not seeing a movie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " you're not? then why did you ask us if we wanted to go?", "answer": " oh umm, that's because i just wanted to y'know walk in on me and chandler while we were, y'know, doing it all night. will you excuse me for just a second?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " okay.  chandler? can i see you for a second?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " uh, yeah.", "answer": " okay.  we have got to beat them! {here we go yet again.}", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " 'cause, gary and phoebe think they're a hotter couple than we are!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " ohh, so?", "answer": " so! so we've got to go upstairs and have a lot of sex to prove them wrong!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  excuse me.  you should check this out, tell the other tenants. apparently he's running around looking for some kind of a hot girl.", "answer": "  who isn't?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i don't, i don't think we've meet. i-i'm ross. the hot girl: i know. you're the guy who wouldn't chip in for the handyman.", "answer": " nevermind!  the hot girl: no, i-i actually thought it was unfair the way everyone reacted. i mean you had just moved in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i had just moved in. thank you! listen umm\u009a the hot girl: jen.", "answer": " jen, i know this may sound a little\u009a but uh, would you maybe wanna grab a cup of coffee sometime, or\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " sure! that would be nice.", "answer": " umm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh! my number is on there.  give me a call.", "answer": " i will give you a call.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " that was amazing!", "answer": " phoebe and gary are so gonna hear about this at dinner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " that was amazing.", "answer": " we are the hottest! huh? no one is hotter than we are! you're the best.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " no, you're the best.", "answer": " no, you're the best.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " no, you're the best.", "answer": " i am the best.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  hey joey! isn't that the girl that waved at you the other day?", "answer": " i don't know. but i can see through your sheet.  yeah, yeah, that's her. but y'know what? doesn't matter, i'm never gonna get to meet her anyway.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " because it's impossible to find her apartment! she lives in some like of hot girl parallel universe, or something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " what are you talking about?  she obviously lives on the second floor, seventh apartment from the left!", "answer": " no. no. no. she lives on the third floor, eighth apartment from the left.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " no, those first two windows,  that's the lobby. and y'know the other one over there, that's the stairway. you've been counting wrong.", "answer": " i did not know that! thank you monica.  i can't believe i almost lost another girl because of counting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " so uhh, you ready?", "answer": " sure, i'll just get my coat.  could you get that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " sure.  joey\u009a", "answer": " dahhhhh!!  no! noooo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " ah, first, i-i would like to say thank you for agreeing to see me again.", "answer": " that's quite all right, but i feel obligated to tell you that this meeting is being videotaped.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  okay. umm, well, first i would like to start by apologizing for kissing you and uh, for yelling at you.", "answer": " fair enough.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " now you're probably going to hire one of the people who did not ah,  who did, who did not umm, yell at you and storm out, and i think that's a big mistake and here's why. i made a huge fool of myself and i came back, that shows courage. when i thought you wanted sex in exchange for this job, i said no. that shows integrity. and, i was not afraid to stand up for myself and that shows courage.  okay umm, now i know i already said courage, but y'know you gotta have courage. and umm, and finally when i thought you were making sexual advances in the workplace, i said no and i was not litigious. {by the way, litigious means to want to litigate and litigate is to make a lawsuit against. so she didn't want to sue him. don't worry, i had to look it up too.} so there you go, you got, you got  courage, you got integrity, you got  courage again, and not litigious. look mr\u009a", "answer": " zelner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " zelner! right! i knew that! i really, really want this job and i think, i think i would be really good at it.", "answer": " y'know what? i may regret this but uh, i'm going to give you a shot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  oh! you are?", "answer": " um-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " really? oh thank you! oh\u009a oh, would it be completely inappropriate to give you a hug?", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " you tired chandler?", "answer": " you better believe he's tired, after the day we had! if you know what i mean. you know what i mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " honey, the tortilla chips know what you mean.", "answer": " so uh chandler, you like that badge i got you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " phoebe, you have a, a twig in your hair.", "answer": " ohh,  umm, we kinda took a little detour on the way over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " yeah, we took a little stroll in the park and no one was around, so\u009a", "answer": " you didn't!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " we did! we violated section 12 paragraph 7 of the criminal code!", "answer": " the park huh? a public place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " i hear ya. excuse me for just a second!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " hi chandler.", "answer": " monica! this is the men's room!  isn't", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " yes it is. you see i've always found the men's bathroom very sexual. haven't you?", "answer": " no. and if i did, i don't think we'd be going out. monica, this is getting ridiculous!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " come on, we can't let them win!", "answer": " ugh, we have already proved that we are hot! okay? so why-why are you getting so obsessed about this thing?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " because phoebe and gary are in that-can't-keep-their-hands-off-each-other-doing-it-in-the-park phase!", "answer": "  so?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i feel really sad that we're not\u009areally there anymore.", "answer": " oh wow! is that what this all have been about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " wasn't it a lot more exciting when we were y'know all over each other all the time?", "answer": " yeah that was great. that was really great! but to tell you the truth, i'm more excited about where we are right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah! i've never been in a relationship that's lasted this long before. y'know to get past the beginning and still be around each other all the time, i think that's pretty incredible. and the fact that this is happening all with you, yeah i think that's pretty exciting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " that is so sweet. i know that i was acting a little crazy but umm, i feel the same way.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " y'know what i just realized? you just freaked out about our relationship.", "answer": " did not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " yes you did! admit it! you freaked out!", "answer": " okay, i freaked out a little.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "  i cannot believe ross is buying this!", "answer": " thank god! i can't watch him anymore!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": "  you guys ready fore the movies?", "answer": " yeah! oh by the way, thank you for loaning us pamela and yasmine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}]